## **ABOUT ME**

I seek to be challenged. I love working with people and building teams. I am a quick leaner, and I believe that hard work, dedication, and positive attitudes lead to success. I am a mother to a wonderful two-year old with special needs.

### **EXPERIENCE**

## KEY ACCOUNT REPRESENTATIVE

# Solenis Canada ULC, Pulp & Paper Division • Jan 2020 - Present

Irving Tissue Company 2020 - 2021, Lake Utopia Paper 2022 - Present

- Organized and executed high level trials and meetings
- Worked with various departments to organize and execute projects
- Provided regular written reports and proposals, managed inventory, made safety and process improvements
- Performed regular lab work and data analysis
- Developed and provided training material, and troubleshooting manuals
- Successfully commissioned new equipment and applications

#### > STUDENT UNION ORIENTATION CHAIR

#### University of New Brunswick Student Union • Jan 2018 - Nov 2018

Successfully planned, organized and executed Orientation Week for over 1000 new students

- Interviewed, selected, trained and managed a leadership team of over 150 people
- Developed an emergency response plan, detailed schedule, and execution plan for all events
- Developed sponsorships and partnerships with local businesses

# > CHEMICAL ENGINEERING STUDENT

# Irving Pulp & Paper Division • May - Aug: 2015, 2016 & 2017

Summer Student Position - Irving Tissue 2017, Irving Pulp & Paper 2016, Irving Paper Ltd. 2015

- Provided technical support to operations and other departments through process improvement projects with a strong emphasis on safety
- Practiced data analysis and problem-solving skills to troubleshoot operational issues
- Developed skills in project management and effective written and verbal communication

## **SKILLS**

#### **TECHNICAL**

- Microsoft Office 365
- ParcView
- Pulp & Paper Experience
- Waste-Water Treatment
  Experience
- Laboratory Procedures & Analysis

#### LEADERSHIP

- Interpersonal Skills
- Organizational Skills
- Time Management
- Written & Verbal
  Communication
- Self-motivated & Selfstarter

## **CERTIFICATES**

- Confined Space (2023)
- WHMIS (2023)
- Lean Six Sigma White Belt Training (2015)

## **EDUCATION**

University of New Brunswick Sept 2014 - May 2019

Bachelor of Science in Chemical Engineering, Minors in Mathematics & Business Administration